battrick.org 2014-11-21

# Battrick - Privacy Statement

The Battrick team has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

We use your IP address to administer our Web site. IP addresses are also logged and used for security purposes, and may be used in abuse investigations or to identify cheaters within the game itself.

We do not use cookies to extract information from you, solely to simplify your visits, mainly by having cookies remember which language and specific part of the site you want to start your visit with. A temporary cookie is also used to keep track of your "session". Without that temporary cookie (that holds no relevant information except a numeric key and which is not stored after you quit your browser) you would have had to log on again on each page. You can turn off cookies in your web browser (more information about this is available at (<http://www.aboutcookies.org/>). This will however make it more or less impossible to access many of the functions on our web site.

We reserve the right to use cookies for the purpose of serving and / or targeting ads, offers and other marketing messages. Presently, however, we don't do this.

No personal customer data is ever shared with the advertising companies.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. It is in the user's interest to submit truthful information, as this is also used to verify the user's right to his or her account.

Demographic and profile data may also collected at our site. This information may shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not currently do this.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers).

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the surveys is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. Battrick is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Battrick will not share customer data with outside companies or sites, even if we have a special relationship with them. Sponsors, business partners, co-branded sites or content providers may get the opportunity to offer products and services to you within the Battrick web site, but we will ask you before passing on any of your personal information to other parties. The only exception is if another company needs the data for the operation of the service and they agree to adhere to our privacy policy.

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and / or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

  * You can send an mail via the Contact Us page.
  * You can visit the preference page when you have logged on.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us through the Contact Us page.
